{
    "id": "281b3441eba44af4ab2668f60b29e7b4",
    "title": "Primary Auxiliaries Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She …………………………. returned yet.",
            "description": "The present perfect is more common with already and yet. Also, use has/have before the past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "isn't",
                "didn't",
                "hasn't"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8fea459edcfb4a91b27c1a2b121e33d8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… know what I should do now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "don't",
                "haven't",
                "aren't"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e1126d5d2eda42aa9965486a14c42d91"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ……………………………. recognize him.",
            "description": "Use a form of do before the infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "aren't",
                "didn't",
                "hasn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1a6f9db795f4419388d2fb04ab2966e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. you received the invite?",
            "description": "Use a form of have before the past participle form of the verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "Have",
                "Are",
                "Do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "04d8a83e15464306983952ed7bc57299"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………….. you see him yesterday?",
            "description": "Use a form of do before the infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "Did",
                "Had",
                "Have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5603f0f511d54f95b139a14487b65276"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where …………………………. she work now?",
            "description": "Use a form of do before the infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "does",
                "has",
                "is"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "87da0c065bad4b49ad163e41e0658e90"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. this your bag?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Is",
                "Has",
                "Does"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9ed20e025616437ea057a144db06f00e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………………….. not understand the consequences of his action.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does",
                "has",
                "is"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "858aafd2dd1a4b69b64e50ea371fd423"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. you call him yesterday?",
            "description": "Use a form of do before the infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "Had",
                "Did",
                "Were"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e1a3fbf3f1eb4ed9a603d7903099f414"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………………… returned the camera he borrowed from me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "didn't",
                "hasn't",
                "wasn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ea155ce2c3f747da8a7daad9058df57a"
        },
        {
            "question": "What …………………………. you do to provoke him?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "had",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "23a736b858634d49a4599dddac253e50"
        },
        {
            "question": "How ………………………… you learn about his accident?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "had",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "42cf762866874b46850de7c0ebed0c18"
        }
    ]
}